<article>
    <author>shelby andrews</author>
    <links href="http://www.allenbwest.com/matt-palumbo/caught-hillary-complete-memory-lapse-camera">
        <end>230</end>
        <start>225</start>
    </links>
    <mainText>Both of the 2016 presidential candidates had their chance to speak out about the recent bombings in New York and New Jersey. There are so many differences between Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton, just in these videos alone. Watch!  What a difference in Donald Trump and Hillary Clinton&#8217;s responses to last night&#8217;s NYC bombing. Trump said, &#8220;I must tell you that just before I got off the plane a bomb went off in New York and nobody knows what&#8217;s going on,&#8221; Trump said during a rally last night at an airport hangar in Colorado Springs, Colorado.&#160;&#8220;But boy we are living in a time &#8212; we better get very tough, folks. We better get very, very tough. It&#8217;s a terrible thing that&#8217;s going on in our world, in our country and we are going to get tough and smart and vigilant.&#8221; These comments came just minutes after the explosion occurred.  Hillary by contrast, looked like she was half asleep (or even drugged) during her response, in which she contradicted herself within a period of forty seconds. At the 0:28 mark in the video below, she states &#8220;&#8220;I&#8217;ve been briefed about the bombings in New York and New Jersey, as well as the attack in Minnesota.&#8221; Then, at 1:08, she was asked &#8220;&#8220;Do you have any reaction to the fact that Donald Trump, prior to taking the stage tonight, called the explosion tonight a bomb, and if that&#8217;s an appropriate&#160;term&#8221;?&#8221; Hillary, apparently unaware that bombings are caused by bombs, replied &#8220;Well I think it&#8217;s important to know the facts about any incident like this, that&#8217;s why it&#8217;s critical to support he first responders, the investigators, who are looking into it to determine what did happen.&#8221;  What could she possibly think was the cause of the explosion? A brain fart? The difference in the professionalism between these two is beyond me. Hillary Clinton is obviously proving herself to not be well enough to run a country. She just needs to drop out and rest.</mainText>
    <orientation>right</orientation>
    <paragraph>
        <end>231</end>
        <start>0</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>232</end>
        <start>232</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>327</end>
        <start>233</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>830</end>
        <start>328</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>831</end>
        <start>831</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1339</end>
        <start>832</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1618</end>
        <start>1340</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1619</end>
        <start>1619</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1695</end>
        <start>1620</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1887</end>
        <start>1696</start>
    </paragraph>
    <portal>I Have The Truth</portal>
    <quotes>
        <end>455</end>
        <start>341</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>766</end>
        <start>547</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1142</end>
        <start>1041</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1336</end>
        <start>1174</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1617</end>
        <start>1412</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>830</end>
        <start>233</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1618</end>
        <start>832</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1695</end>
        <start>1620</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>36</end>
        <start>-1</start>
    </quotes>
    <title>Hillary Caught On Camera Having COMPLETE Memory Lapse During Reaction To Recent BOMBINGS&#8230;</title>
    <uri>https://ihavethetruth.com/2016/09/18/hillary-caught-on-camera-having-complete-memory-lapse-during-reaction-to-recent-bombings/</uri>
    <veracity>mixture of true and false</veracity>
<number_of_quotes>9</number_of_quotes><number_of_links>1</number_of_links><contains_author>1</contains_author><number_of_words>342</number_of_words><number_of_unique_words>183</number_of_unique_words><number_of_long_words>62</number_of_long_words><number_of_monosyllable_words>264</number_of_monosyllable_words><number_of_polsyllable_words>26</number_of_polsyllable_words><number_of_syllables>455</number_of_syllables><flesch_readability_ease>82.31236842105264</flesch_readability_ease></article>