<article>
    <author>Amber</author>
    <links href="http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2016/09/19/obama-to-speak-in-nyc-after-glossing-over-attack-during-manhattan-fundraiser.html">
        <end>162</end>
        <start>149</start>
    </links>
    <links href="http://freedomdaily.com/islamic-terrorism-ied-rocks-nyc-as-explosion-maims-twenty-nine-people/">
        <end>812</end>
        <start>799</start>
    </links>
    <mainText>Saturday Obama gave a speech to the Black Congressional Caucus where he had ample opportunity to give courage to Americans in a scary time. However, he didn&#8217;t say anything about the recent attacks then and as of noon (East Coast Time) Monday, President Barack Obama has made ZERO comments on the string of terrorist attacks hitting cities in the United States. Over the weekend there were a number of terror attacks in the name of &#8216;allah&#8217; that has devastated some communities and killed or injured dozens of people. Check out the list below and tell me if you think the President should have made a speech Saturday, Sunday or especially today to give solace to the victims families and communities being terrorized? Watch the latest video at &lt;a href=&#8221;http://video.foxnews.com&#8221;&gt;video.foxnews.com&lt;/a&gt; Freedom Daily reported earlier: New Jersey, 8am Saturday Suspect: Ahmad Rahami (arrested), possible 4 other suspects in custody from Afghanistan 3 pipe bombs wired together in a dumpster in New Jersey targeting a 5k run for Marines. Minnesota, 8pm Saturday Suspect: Dahir Adan (fatally wounded) Muslim man went on a stabbing spree&#8230; stabbing eight people before being shot by police. New York, 8:40pm Saturday Suspect: Ahmad Rahami (arrested), possible 4 other suspects in custody from Afghanistan Manhattan a bomb went off injuring 29 people. Pressure cooker was found with wiring and a timing device. New York, 3:00am Sunday Suspect: Ahmad Rahami (arrested), possible 4 other suspects in custody from Afghanistan Explosive device was found around the Chelsea area. THIS just in- New Jersey, 1am Monday Suspect: Ahmad Rahami (arrested), possible 4 other suspects in custody from Afghanistan Pipe Bomb explodes near a New Jersey train station. I have watched Obama NOT lead for nearly 8 years. His lack of guts, integrity and leadership is the greatest reason that Muslim extremists feel brave enough to walk around American streets with bombs and set them wherever they want. The United States needs a real President who can LEAD America in a time of crisis. If you don&#8217;t believe we are in crisis, we are in greater trouble than I thought. </mainText>
    <orientation>right</orientation>
    <paragraph>
        <end>715</end>
        <start>0</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>798</end>
        <start>716</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1031</end>
        <start>799</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1181</end>
        <start>1032</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1400</end>
        <start>1182</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1564</end>
        <start>1401</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>2138</end>
        <start>1565</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>2139</end>
        <start>2139</start>
    </paragraph>
    <portal>Freedom Daily</portal>
    <quotes>
        <end>812</end>
        <start>799</start>
    </quotes>
    <title>Speaking In NY, Obama Shocks Americans With What He Says About Attacks</title>
    <uri>http://freedomdaily.com/speaking-in-ny-obama-shocks-americans-with-what-he-says-about-attacks/</uri>
    <veracity>mixture of true and false</veracity>
<number_of_quotes>1</number_of_quotes><number_of_links>2</number_of_links><contains_author>1</contains_author><number_of_words>354</number_of_words><number_of_unique_words>207</number_of_unique_words><number_of_long_words>87</number_of_long_words><number_of_monosyllable_words>223</number_of_monosyllable_words><number_of_polsyllable_words>47</number_of_polsyllable_words><number_of_syllables>542</number_of_syllables><flesch_readability_ease>56.17030408773681</flesch_readability_ease><number_of_sentences>17</number_of_sentences><first_person_pronouns>5</first_person_pronouns><second_person_pronouns>2</second_person_pronouns><third_person_pronouns>2</third_person_pronouns><average_number_of_syllables>31.88235294117647</average_number_of_syllables><conjunction_count>9</conjunction_count><modal_verb_count>3</modal_verb_count><number_of_hedge_words>19</number_of_hedge_words><number_of_weasel_words>21</number_of_weasel_words></article>