<article>
    <author />
    <links href="http://www.politico.com/story/2015/09/clinton-abedin-state-job-approved-214038#ixzz4KYuDW8UF">
        <end>20</end>
        <start>13</start>
    </links>
    <mainText>As WikiLeaks reports, the plan was to make Abedin Secretary of State. As President, Hillary Clinton will appoint Huma Abedin as Secretary of State. This according to leaked e mails between Abedin, Mrs. Clinton, and Clinton&#8217;s former chief of staff Cheryl Mills. Abedin, 40, would be the first Moslem Secretary of State, and one of the youngest ever. She would not, however, be the first foreign born Secretary of State. Henry Kissinger, 93, has that distinction, having been appointed by Richard Nixon. Huma Mahmood Abedin, 40, served as vice chairwoman of Hillary Clinton&#8217;s 2016 campaign for President. Prior to that, she served as the deputy chief of staff to U.S. Secretary of State Hillary Clinton from 2009 to 2013. ABedin parlayed a 1996 Whitehouse internship into a role as Mrs. Clinton&#8217;s Right Hand Man, or Woman. Former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton is listed as the supervisor certifying Abedin&#8217;s designation as a &#8220;special government employee. This classification allowed Abedin to work for an outside consulting firm and the Clinton Foundation, at the same time that she advised then Secretary of State Clinton. The Clinton campaign reiterated Sunday that Clinton did not personally sign documents for Abedin, or other employees. Hillary Clinton&#8217;s name was listed in print, but the signature underneath was redacted by the State Department. The document caused a stir and led to media reports Clinton had lied about not having been involved.. As you can see, the Clintons play &#8220;cover your ass&#8221; at every turn. They do whatever it takes to get what they need to accomplish without getting their own hands dirty. </mainText>
    <orientation>right</orientation>
    <paragraph>
        <end>69</end>
        <start>0</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>260</end>
        <start>70</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>501</end>
        <start>261</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>719</end>
        <start>502</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>820</end>
        <start>720</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1126</end>
        <start>821</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1457</end>
        <start>1127</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1624</end>
        <start>1458</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1625</end>
        <start>1625</start>
    </paragraph>
    <portal>The Black Sphere</portal>
    <quotes>
        <end>1507</end>
        <start>929</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1457</end>
        <start>70</start>
    </quotes>
    <title>WikiLeaks: Clinton Would Make Abedin Secretary of State</title>
    <uri>http://theblacksphere.net/2016/09/wikileaks-clinton-make-abedin-secretary-state/</uri>
    <veracity>mixture of true and false</veracity>
<number_of_quotes>2</number_of_quotes><number_of_links>1</number_of_links><contains_author>1</contains_author><number_of_words>270</number_of_words><number_of_unique_words>153</number_of_unique_words><number_of_long_words>74</number_of_long_words><number_of_monosyllable_words>177</number_of_monosyllable_words><number_of_polsyllable_words>33</number_of_polsyllable_words><number_of_syllables>404</number_of_syllables><flesch_readability_ease>65.02333333333337</flesch_readability_ease><number_of_sentences>18</number_of_sentences><first_person_pronouns>1</first_person_pronouns><second_person_pronouns>1</second_person_pronouns><third_person_pronouns>6</third_person_pronouns><average_number_of_syllables>22.444444444444443</average_number_of_syllables><conjunction_count>7</conjunction_count><modal_verb_count>4</modal_verb_count></article>