<article>
    <author>Posted by Conover Kennard on 22 Sep 2016</author>
    <links href="http://bigstory.ap.org/article/14ce6ee113ff47f894fb1e7e3fcb3892/tulsa-police-officer-charged-mans-death?utm_campaign=SocialFlow&amp;utm_source=Twitter&amp;utm_medium=AP">
        <end>162</end>
        <start>155</start>
    </links>
    <links href="https://twitter.com/AP/status/779057226073931776">
        <end>1389</end>
        <start>1371</start>
    </links>
    <mainText>Terence Crutcher, 40, was shot once and killed by Tulsa police officer Betty Shelby at around 7:40 p.m. Friday. Before the fatal shooting, police&#160;received reports of an abandoned vehicle blocking a road. On Monday, the police department released aerial video of the incident. Shelby&#8217;s husband and an unidentified pilot are heard telling each other than they believe the &#8220;black dude&#8221; was dangerous and &#8220;needed to be tasered.&#8221; It was later discovered that Mr. Crutcher&#160;was unarmed. He wasn&#8217;t a danger and his arms were in the air when he was shot dead by Officer Shelby. Crutcher&#8217;s&#160;vehicle had stalled in the street and was seeking assistance. The Associated Press reports: Prosecutors in Tulsa, Oklahoma, have filed first-degree manslaughter charges against the white police officer who fatally shot an unarmed black man on a city street. District Attorney Steve Kunzweiler filed the charges Thursday against officer Betty Shelby, who shot and killed 40-year-old Terence Crutcher&#160;on Sept. 16. Dashcam and aerial footage of the shooting and its aftermath showed Crutcher&#160;walking away from Shelby with his arms in the air. Shelby had a stun gun on her at the time but chose not to use it and instead, opted for deadly force. BREAKING: Prosecutor announces 1st-degree manslaughter charges against Tulsa officer who fatally shot Terence Crutcher. &#8212; The Associated Press (@AP) September 22, 2016  Officer Shelby has quite a history. When applying for a job with the sheriff&#8217;s office, she described previous marijuana use. In addition, she admitted to&#160;two previous domestic-related incidents involving the courts. She told of a 1993 incident in which she and&#160;her boyfriend at the time damaged each other&#8217;s vehicles when they were breaking up. Both filed temporary restraining orders that were subsequently dismissed. And then there&#8217;s a 2002 incident in which she said&#160;her ex-husband&#8217;s new wife filed a protective order which claimed that Shelby made harassing phone calls to her. Later, the protective order was later denied, according to what Shelby said in her application. &#8220;The Judge saw that I was not guilty of the accusations made against me,&#8221; she stated at the time. On Monday, the department said that Shelby is on paid administrative leave. That&#8217;s the protocol for a shooting at the hands of a police officer. And today, she faces first-degree manslaughter charges. Video of the incident: If the police shooting of Terence&#160;Crutcher is acceptable to you, then you need to reevaluate your life.</mainText>
    <orientation>left</orientation>
    <paragraph>
        <end>424</end>
        <start>0</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>641</end>
        <start>425</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>671</end>
        <start>642</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>837</end>
        <start>672</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1119</end>
        <start>838</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1221</end>
        <start>1120</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1341</end>
        <start>1222</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1389</end>
        <start>1342</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1390</end>
        <start>1390</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1809</end>
        <start>1391</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1972</end>
        <start>1810</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>2166</end>
        <start>1973</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>2367</end>
        <start>2167</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>2390</end>
        <start>2368</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>2494</end>
        <start>2391</start>
    </paragraph>
    <portal>Winning Democrats</portal>
    <quotes>
        <end>381</end>
        <start>371</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>423</end>
        <start>402</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>2141</end>
        <start>2070</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1119</end>
        <start>672</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1389</end>
        <start>1222</start>
    </quotes>
    <title />
    <uri>http://winningdemocrats.com/the-cop-who-murdered-terence-crutcher-just-got-some-very-very-bad-news-video/</uri>
    <veracity>mostly true</veracity>
<number_of_quotes>5</number_of_quotes><number_of_links>2</number_of_links><contains_author>1</contains_author><number_of_words>418</number_of_words><number_of_unique_words>206</number_of_unique_words><number_of_long_words>112</number_of_long_words><number_of_monosyllable_words>272</number_of_monosyllable_words><number_of_polsyllable_words>58</number_of_polsyllable_words><number_of_syllables>634</number_of_syllables><flesch_readability_ease>64.37592025518342</flesch_readability_ease><number_of_sentences>30</number_of_sentences><first_person_pronouns>1</first_person_pronouns><second_person_pronouns>2</second_person_pronouns><third_person_pronouns>14</third_person_pronouns></article>