<article>
    <author>Jeff Dunetz</author>
    <links href="http://lidblog.com/birtherism-an-semi-illustrated-history-part-1-roots-in-clinton-campaign/">
        <end>1443</end>
        <start>1387</start>
    </links>
    <mainText>The mainstream media got played today and it was wonderful.&#160;The Trump&#160;campaign released a statement last night saying their candidate believed Barack Obama was born in the United States, but they didn&#8217;t believe it. This morning the campaign announced that Trump will make a statement about the birther issue and they all rushed to his new DC hotel for the press conference. But Trump didn&#8217;t come out right away. First the press had to listen to (and in some cases televise) a series of Medal of Honor winners praising the GOP candidate. &#160;And when they were all done Trump came out and said: &#8220;Hillary Clinton and her campaign of 2008 started the birther controversy. I finished it. President Barack Obama was born in the United States, period. Now we all want to get back to making America strong and great again.&#8221; With that it was over. The press didn&#8217;t get to ask about Trump&#8217;s claims that Hillary&#8217;s campaign started it and he finished it&#8230;Trump was gone and it was great! Let&#8217;s get to the real issues. Did Hillary Clinton and/or her 2008 campaign start the birtherism and did Trump end it? The story is too long to complete in one post, therefore consider this&#160;Part 1, Birtherism&#8217;s Roots in Clinton Campaign There is no evidence that Hillary Clinton ever said publicly that she believes Barack Obama wasn&#8217;t a natural born citizen. But there is plenty of evidence that the birther hoax&#8230; Read the rest of the story at Jeff Dunetz&#8217;s blog The Lid  The views expressed in this opinion article are solely those of their author and are not necessarily either shared or endorsed by EagleRising.com Get your daily dose of Eagle Rising by entering your email address below.</mainText>
    <orientation>right</orientation>
    <paragraph>
        <end>590</end>
        <start>0</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>813</end>
        <start>591</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>972</end>
        <start>814</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1090</end>
        <start>973</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1208</end>
        <start>1091</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1386</end>
        <start>1209</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1443</end>
        <start>1387</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1444</end>
        <start>1444</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1590</end>
        <start>1445</start>
    </paragraph>
    <paragraph>
        <end>1664</end>
        <start>1591</start>
    </paragraph>
    <portal>Eagle Rising</portal>
    <quotes>
        <end>812</end>
        <start>592</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>813</end>
        <start>591</start>
    </quotes>
    <quotes>
        <end>1626</end>
        <start>1614</start>
    </quotes>
    <title>The TRUE Roots of the Birther Movement, Part I</title>
    <uri>http://eaglerising.com/36831/the-true-roots-of-the-birther-movement-part-i/</uri>
    <veracity>mostly true</veracity>
<number_of_quotes>3</number_of_quotes><number_of_links>1</number_of_links><contains_author>1</contains_author><number_of_words>300</number_of_words><number_of_unique_words>162</number_of_unique_words><number_of_long_words>58</number_of_long_words><number_of_monosyllable_words>222</number_of_monosyllable_words><number_of_polsyllable_words>17</number_of_polsyllable_words><number_of_syllables>399</number_of_syllables><flesch_readability_ease>80.47609090909093</flesch_readability_ease><number_of_sentences>22</number_of_sentences><first_person_pronouns>2</first_person_pronouns><second_person_pronouns>0</second_person_pronouns><third_person_pronouns>13</third_person_pronouns><average_number_of_syllables>18.136363636363637</average_number_of_syllables><conjunction_count>15</conjunction_count><modal_verb_count>1</modal_verb_count><number_of_hedge_words>14</number_of_hedge_words><number_of_weasel_words>23</number_of_weasel_words></article>